<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Religions of Rimworld 2.0: Children of Atom</name>
	<author>ZzZombo, Rick Grymes</author>
	<url></url>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.1</li>
		<li>1.2</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>basarab.ror</packageId>
			<displayName>Religions of Rimworld 2.0</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/basarab1504/ReligionsOfRimworld-2.0/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=1974112020</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>basarab.ror</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<packageId>ZzZombo.commission.ChildrenOfAtom</packageId>
	<description>Adds a new religion for "Religions of Rimworld 2.0".\n\nThe religion of the Children of Atom is centered around the eponymous Atom and the idea that within every atomic mass in all of creation exists an entire universe. When that atomic mass is split, that universe divides and becomes two. As such, Atom is a creator deity, creating new worlds through the act of nuclear fission (referred to by the Children as Division). As a result, the Great War is seen and cherished as a divine event that created uncountable new universes in one instant. It represents creation and unification in Atom's Glow - radiation. The Children worship Atom by worshiping radiation, his Glow, emphasizing its ability to transform and create something better. Through it, they can achieve the aforementioned Division, as the Glow breaks them apart and they are reborn, releasing all of the worlds within them. While obliteration through nuclear explosions is a preferred means of achieving Division, death of natural causes or irradiation is considered perfectly in line with the Children's teachings. To maintain their devotion and worship, the Children tend to seek out irradiated areas to set up shrines and other centers of worship, which double as staging areas for proselytizing efforts and crusades against the unfaithful. They will also seek out and defend any stockpiles of nuclear weapons, to prevent their disposal or use in a manner not consistent with the tenets of the teachings of Atom.</description>
</ModMetaData>
